[SPEAKER_01]: Valley Alliant Palms, this is Rebecca.
[SPEAKER_01]: What is your maintenance emergency?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, ma'am.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's a, my bathroom is flooding.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's like a plumbing broken or something and it's flooding everywhere.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, what is broken in your bathroom?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's like a pipe, the pipe that's connected to the toilet.
[SPEAKER_01]: Are you able to turn off the water valve?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, it's broken.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: What apartment?
211.
[SPEAKER_01]: 211.
[SPEAKER_01]: What's your name?
[SPEAKER_00]: Griselda.
[SPEAKER_01]: Griselda.
[SPEAKER_01]: And your phone number is 956-252-3979?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll go ahead and I'll go ahead and let them know.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you.